And for our last project,
this is the SkillGap application.
So here, you can go ahead and upload
a job posting or a resume
and go ahead and find the gaps.
And the problem that we're trying to solve
here
is that, you know, job rejections
don't really tell you what you missed.
SkillGap goes a step above that
and just outlines exactly what you're
missing
from the requirements
and generates an actionable two-week
recovery plan.
So, here it's going ahead
and reading both documents, finding
the difference between the two documents,
and then drafting the output.
So the first thing that you'll see up here
is
a 0 to 100 score
based on how well you meet the
requirements.
Down here, the requirements,
whether you meet them,
somewhat meet them,
or do not meet them at all.
And then down here you can see it's
drafting
a two-week plan to fill in those gaps.
And so for this two-week plan,
you can see here it outlines exactly
what the task is,
what the output would look like,
and then a link to helpful documentation.
And so for this one,
we did keep everything local, again,
to use the information that we have
and that the user can provide.
It's also not currently scaled for online
use,
which might be a feature that comes in
new...